Hi all.
This is Sonali from Sumago
Infotech Private Limited.
So today I'm here to announce our new
venture, which is a Scope, scope as a
Sumago Center of Practical Excellence.
So this is our new venture that
we have started for the fresher.
This is a major milestone for
our organization and we are
very confident it will be a game
changer for our organization.
So our goal with the scope is to create
a hub for the practical expertises for
the innovation and for the startups.
So those who want to start
their career in the IT sector.
This is this platform for you.
So this platform is, specially for
the fresher, for the students who
is graduate ungraduate but those who
want to start their career in IT,
they can choose this platform scope.
So Scope is a Sumago Center
of Practical Excellence.
So we have identified some key
areas, where we are working.
Including artificial intelligence,
machine learning, data science, then
blockchain and robotic process automation.
So this is a latest technology and this
is very demanding for the industry.
So yes, guys, you can start your career
with the scope, which is totally practical
oriented innovation for the Freshers.
And we want to thanks to
everybody for their hard work and
dedication in making this happen.
So thanks to all the team member
of Sumago for make it happen.
Stay tuned for more updates.
Thank you.